[{"answer": "I think the tide has turned.", "docId": "120329pmt", "aSentId": 38, "question": "Why do you want to do this interview?", "qSentId": 37}, {"answer": "Oh, yes.", "docId": "120329pmt", "aSentId": 44, "question": "Has your family had death threats?", "qSentId": 43}, {"answer": "Credible threats.", "docId": "120329pmt", "aSentId": 48, "question": "Credible threats?", "qSentId": 47}, {"answer": "You know, I'm really not at liberty to discuss exactly who was threatened or how they were threatened, but I can tell you that I, myself, have been contacted by law enforcement, too, because there was credible intelligence that could threaten me.", "docId": "120329pmt", "aSentId": 53, "question": "Against others?", "qSentId": 52}, {"answer": "Well, you know, taking, from what you said, when you said chasing after and getting into an altercation, there's a lot of ways that people get into altercations.", "docId": "120329pmt", "aSentId": 76, "question": "Why would your brother do that?", "qSentId": 75}, {"answer": "Me, personally, I heard immediately after the incident.", "docId": "120329pmt", "aSentId": 83, "question": "You, personally?", "qSentId": 82}, {"answer": "I would say within 24 hours.", "docId": "120329pmt", "aSentId": 86, "question": "Within an hour?", "qSentId": 85}, {"answer": "Would be the closest I'm willing to narrow the window down of exactly when George spoke, yes, would be within the next 24 hours.", "docId": "120329pmt", "aSentId": 89, "question": "So the next day?", "qSentId": 88}, {"answer": "Well, some of the details have come out.", "docId": "120329pmt", "aSentId": 91, "question": "And what exactly did he tell you about what happened?", "qSentId": 90}, {"answer": "Down towards the entrance of the neighborhood.", "docId": "120329pmt", "aSentId": 106, "question": "Which way is he running?", "qSentId": 105}, {"answer": "I believe that's what George -- and that's what's in the police reports and that's what has been leaked and --", "docId": "120329pmt", "aSentId": 122, "question": "When you say he stopped following, how do you know that?", "qSentId": 121}, {"answer": "Right.", "docId": "120329pmt", "aSentId": 126, "question": "Wouldn't it?", "qSentId": 125}, {"answer": "Correct.", "docId": "120329pmt", "aSentId": 130, "question": "It's only George's word, isn't it?", "qSentId": 129}, {"answer": "What has come out that I can talk about today is that Trayvon Martin somehow snuck up on him, and according to Mr. Crump, their own attorney, he was on -- we don't know if this is verifiable information, but he was on the phone with his girlfriend.", "docId": "120329pmt", "aSentId": 136, "question": "What did George tell you Trayvon Martin allegedly did to him?", "qSentId": 135}, {"answer": "One of those things.", "docId": "120329pmt", "aSentId": 143, "question": "What did George tell you he say?", "qSentId": 142}, {"answer": "Well, I don't know, I believe that at the time, George knew he had sustained some kind of injury to his face or his nose.", "docId": "120329pmt", "aSentId": 150, "question": "And when you say \"attacked,\" what did George tell you Trayvon did to him?", "qSentId": 149}, {"answer": "We're confident the medical records are going to explain all of George's medical history, because how he was treated at the scene and how he was not.", "docId": "120329pmt", "aSentId": 161, "question": "How do you explain that?", "qSentId": 160}, {"answer": "I'm not at liberty to say.", "docId": "120329pmt", "aSentId": 166, "question": "Have you talked to George about the video since it came out?", "qSentId": 165}, {"answer": "His nose is still broken.", "docId": "120329pmt", "aSentId": 172, "question": "Does he have any injuries now?", "qSentId": 171}, {"answer": "His nose is still broken, yes.", "docId": "120329pmt", "aSentId": 174, "question": "It's still broken?", "qSentId": 173}, {"answer": "His nose.", "docId": "120329pmt", "aSentId": 176, "question": "A month later, it's still broken?", "qSentId": 175}, {"answer": "Well, and -- you know, I take a -- I take a pause to that whole, you know, conjecture, again, of pulled out a gun and shot him.", "docId": "120329pmt", "aSentId": 196, "question": "Would you not, at the very least, if you're honest and candid about this, would you not have expected that person to at least be arrested, to at least perhaps face some kind of trial where the full evidence could come out?", "qSentId": 195}, {"answer": "No, it is not what happened.", "docId": "120329pmt", "aSentId": 200, "question": "That's not what happened, then?", "qSentId": 199}, {"answer": "Well, he stopped someone from disarming him and shooting him.", "docId": "120329pmt", "aSentId": 202, "question": "But he did pull out a gun and shoot him, right?", "qSentId": 201}, {"answer": "He had a permit to carry that gun --", "docId": "120329pmt", "aSentId": 206, "question": "But he had the gun on him, right?", "qSentId": 205}, {"answer": "The gun, I believe, was in his -- inside -- tucked inside his pant waist --", "docId": "120329pmt", "aSentId": 208, "question": "Where was the gun?", "qSentId": 207}, {"answer": "Well, he has taken control of his firearm, he prevented his firearm from being taken from him and used against him.", "docId": "120329pmt", "aSentId": 212, "question": "So he has pulled it out and he has fired it?", "qSentId": 211}, {"answer": "My father also is on record yesterday night saying that.", "docId": "120329pmt", "aSentId": 217, "question": "That Trayvon was trying to grab his gun to use against him?", "qSentId": 216}, {"answer": "Maybe both.", "docId": "120329pmt", "aSentId": 238, "question": "UNIDENTIFIED 911 DISPATCHER: Do you need police, fire, or medical?", "qSentId": 237}, {"answer": "That's my brother.", "docId": "120329pmt", "aSentId": 255, "question": "Who was screaming there, Robert?", "qSentId": 254}, {"answer": "It could have been anything.", "docId": "120329pmt", "aSentId": 280, "question": "What else could it have been?", "qSentId": 279}, {"answer": "That part -- that tape, it's my understanding, is not actually in the original 911 tapes.", "docId": "120329pmt", "aSentId": 288, "question": "What do you think he's saying?", "qSentId": 287}, {"answer": "Right, I believe --", "docId": "120329pmt", "aSentId": 303, "question": "What do you think you heard?", "qSentId": 302}, {"answer": "IMMERMAN: Again, I just -- I don't believe that, first of all, that they're words.", "docId": "120329pmt", "aSentId": 305, "question": "Or what do you think those two words were?", "qSentId": 304}, {"answer": "I have no idea that he was even saying anything.", "docId": "120329pmt", "aSentId": 308, "question": "But what do you believe he was saying?", "qSentId": 307}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120329pmt", "aSentId": 324, "question": "Have you ever heard your brother utter a racist remark about anybody?", "qSentId": 323}, {"answer": "Well, you know, sadly, even your statements now are just a product of conjecture.", "docId": "120329pmt", "aSentId": 338, "question": "I mean, you can't blame Trayvon Martin for wondering what the hell this guy's doing or who he is?", "qSentId": 337}, {"answer": "Yes, absolutely not.", "docId": "120329pmt", "aSentId": 362, "question": "Do you believe that it was actually, with hindsight, a mistake for the police to effectively conclude on the night, he had no case to answer?", "qSentId": 361}, {"answer": "Not to my knowledge, no.", "docId": "120329pmt", "aSentId": 367, "question": "Has George ever lied to you?", "qSentId": 366}, {"answer": "He's -- he would be the more honest of the two.", "docId": "120329pmt", "aSentId": 369, "question": "He's always been completely, 100 percent honest?", "qSentId": 368}, {"answer": "Well, to his mother, you know, personally, myself, I can't speak for George, this is a tragedy.", "docId": "120329pmt", "aSentId": 377, "question": "To his mother in particular?", "qSentId": 376}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "120329pmt", "aSentId": 408, "question": "What did you make of the interview that I just had with George Zimmerman's brother?", "qSentId": 407}, {"answer": "I don't know what happened.", "docId": "120329pmt", "aSentId": 415, "question": "What do you think happened, from everything you've seen and read?", "qSentId": 414}, {"answer": "Well, I just know that young man shouldn't be dead from this ordeal.", "docId": "120329pmt", "aSentId": 417, "question": "Do you believe that any kind of altercation, if Trayvon was unarmed, justifies somebody shooting him?", "qSentId": 416}, {"answer": "It doesn't matter what I believe or not.", "docId": "120329pmt", "aSentId": 427, "question": "Do you believe that?", "qSentId": 426}, {"answer": "To go for it.", "docId": "120329pmt", "aSentId": 437, "question": "How did he know that he had a gun?", "qSentId": 436}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "120329pmt", "aSentId": 447, "question": "Is this a law that should exist?", "qSentId": 446}, {"answer": "There's a great possibility, yes.", "docId": "120329pmt", "aSentId": 462, "question": "Do you think America, Mike, has become more or less racist since Barack Obama, an African-American, became president?", "qSentId": 461}, {"answer": "One hundred percent, yes.", "docId": "120329pmt", "aSentId": 464, "question": "That it's become worse?", "qSentId": 463}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "120329pmt", "aSentId": 472, "question": "How do you think Barack Obama's doing as president?", "qSentId": 471}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "120329pmt", "aSentId": 478, "question": "Now that your life has changed, and you have to pay bills, and you have to think about money and all those things, very different to when you had half a billion dollars and so on -- now that you're in that position and you can relate probably much better to people on the street, going through hardship, not having jobs and so on, do you think America is coming out of the bad times or do you think that it's still pretty set in the bad times?", "qSentId": 477}, {"answer": "That's -- like that -- you can't even fathom the ways.", "docId": "120329pmt", "aSentId": 520, "question": "How has she changed you?", "qSentId": 519}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "120329pmt", "aSentId": 533, "question": "What effect did that tragedy have on you, did you think?", "qSentId": 532}, {"answer": "I don't know about that.", "docId": "120329pmt", "aSentId": 542, "question": "To be a parent and losing a child, it's so unnatural, isn't it?", "qSentId": 541}, {"answer": "I'm trying to become more understanding.", "docId": "120329pmt", "aSentId": 562, "question": "What kind of parent have you become?", "qSentId": 561}, {"answer": "No, I just miss having this whole ordeal with my family that I never had before.", "docId": "120329pmt", "aSentId": 575, "question": "Do you miss that kind of wealth, or is it destructive, that kind of money?", "qSentId": 574}, {"answer": "I don't know if I'm ever at peace with myself.", "docId": "120329pmt", "aSentId": 582, "question": "How has she made you come to peace with yourself?", "qSentId": 581}, {"answer": "Periodically.", "docId": "120329pmt", "aSentId": 586, "question": "Do you still feel rages, occasionally, like you used to?", "qSentId": 585}, {"answer": "Well, I don't know.", "docId": "120329pmt", "aSentId": 593, "question": "When you look back at your life, what is the period you're most ashamed of?", "qSentId": 592}, {"answer": "Well, of course I'm not that way anymore.", "docId": "120329pmt", "aSentId": 610, "question": "When you look back on that, is that part of the problem, that you have people who just, they make money out of you being like that?", "qSentId": 609}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "120329pmt", "aSentId": 642, "question": "What reaction have you had from people to that?", "qSentId": 641}, {"answer": "YSON: I don't know.", "docId": "120329pmt", "aSentId": 670, "question": "If I could replay a moment for you now, you could relive, what would it be?", "qSentId": 669}, {"answer": "No, he'll find something else wrong.", "docId": "120329pmt", "aSentId": 677, "question": "Do you think Cus D'Amato, who was this legendary trainer -- do you think he would look at the way Mike Tyson is today and feel that you finally worked that out?", "qSentId": 676}, {"answer": "He'd be very happy by the way I'm trying to rebuild my relationship with my children and stuff.", "docId": "120329pmt", "aSentId": 680, "question": "But he'd be proud of you, wouldn't he, for the way that you have rebuilt your life?", "qSentId": 679}, {"answer": "There's no doubt about it.", "docId": "120329pmt", "aSentId": 684, "question": "Was he the father figure that you never really had?", "qSentId": 683}, {"answer": "No doubt about it, because that was my goal.", "docId": "120329pmt", "aSentId": 687, "question": "When you have that kind of respect from somebody like him, it makes all the difference, doesn't it?", "qSentId": 686}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "120329pmt", "aSentId": 693, "question": "When you became world champion for the first time, what did that moment feel like for you?", "qSentId": 692}]